http://www.aiim.org/global%20pages/privacy-policy

Become a Sponsor
Looking for a Speaker?
hello@aiim.org
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for aiim.org and other AIIM online properties, collectively referred to as aiim.org. Because this website wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices. By displaying this statement, this website has agreed to notify you of:
1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website
2. The organization collecting the information
3. How the information is used
4. With whom the information may be shared
5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under AIIM International control
7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact Customer Services, email at hello@aiim.org or by phone at 301-587-8202.
Information Collection and Use
AIIM International is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. AIIM International collects information from our users at several different points on our website.
Orders and Registrations
We request information from the user on our various order and registration forms. Here, a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.
Cookies
This website stores cookies on the user’s computer. These cookies are used to improve our website and provide more personalized services to the user, both on this website and through other media. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site and control vital features of the site, such as personalization and the type of value-added content that is suggested or offered during your browsing experience.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Data collected allows us to provide site enhancements and troubleshoot problems.
Registered User Accounts
Our portal operates under the notion of a registered user of the site to provide relevant, personalized content and access to premium content. All of the information obtained during your registration and, subsequently, contained in your website user account are available only to AIIM staff for purposes of customer service and account management. Any information that personally identifies you or your use of our site is not released to any third party.
Sharing
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and trade members. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.
We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
We partner with other outside parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services.
These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that AIIM International is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
Newsletters and Listserv
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletters and/or Listserv, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Any other survey or contest that deviates from this stated policy will explicitly state this from the survey or contest page.
Security
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.
When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. To learn more about SSL, please see the Verisign website, the provider of our secure certificates.
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees use workstation locking to protect access to their personal workstation when not at their desks. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, all employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked door. User data is not stored on individual workstations or notebook computers.
If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to hello@aiim.org.
Site and Service Updates
We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Registered users of the website and Members of AIIM International are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.
Correction/Updating Personal Information:
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the update information page or by emailing our Customer Support at hello@aiim.org.
Choice/Opt-out
Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, an order form may have an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want to be notified of changes, promotions or be sent any additional correspondence, can keep their email address off of our lists.
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at hello@aiim.org.
Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
For citizens of the European Union and those subject to GDPR:
When using our website and submitting personal data to us as defined in the GDPR, you are entitled to the following rights:
The right of access
You have the right to get confirmation that your personal data is being processed and have the ability to access your personal data.
The right to rectification
You have the right to have your personal data corrected if it is inaccurate or incomplete.
The right to erasure (right to be forgotten)
You have the right to request the removal or deletion of your personal data if there is no compelling reason for us to continue processing it.
The right to restrict processing
You have a right to ‘block’ or restrict the processing of your personal data. When your personal data is restricted, we are permitted to store your data, but not to process it further.
The right to data portability
You have the right to request and get your personal data that you provided to us and use it for your own purposes. We will provide your data to you within 30 days of your request. To request your personal data, please contact us using the information at the top of this privacy notice.
The right to object
You have the right to object to us processing your personal data for the following reasons:
Processing was based on legitimate interests or the performance of a task in the public interest/exercise of official authority (including profiling);
Direct marketing (including profiling);
Processing for purposes of scientific/historical research and statistics; and
Rights in relation to automated decision-making and profiling.
Automated individual decision-making and profiling
You will have the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects concerning you or similarly significantly affects you.
To make these requests, please email hello@aiim.org providing your name and email addresses. Proper identification will be required before any action is taken.
Back to Top
